Brother, the milk is finished.  How to make tea?
You just sit here.
Why is this donkey insulting me in front of the guest
?  Take this money and go and get cow's
milk.
[laughs]
Brother, I need half a litre of milk, please give it to me.
Chotu, it's cow's lunch time now.  Come later.
[laughter]
Brother, it's lunch time for the cow too.  It is not giving milk.
What should I say on this?
Hey, do one thing, go and get powdered milk from the shop.
Yes, okay, I am going.
[Music]
Brother, please give me powdered milk.
Chhotu, the milk powder has just finished.   I have just gone to get it.
[laughter]
Brother, the shop is out of milk too.
Where should I take it from?
I don't know where you will get the milk from.  If
you want to bring milk, you have to bring it.
What should I do?  Where should I get milk from?
Idea.  Brother brought the milk.
Hey, what are you telling us?  Go and
make tea quickly.  Hmm?
Yes, okay.  I will make it now.  [Music]
Here, brother, have some tea.
Take it.
But one second.
Brother, the tea is very tasty.  Which
milk tea have I made today?
Brother, I have made tea from bitch's milk.
this is